# Rivo Juicer Wowor









# Summary

An experienced Computer Science student in Universitas Multimedia Nusantara with a big passion for studying and lecturing, alongside with demonstrated history of working in the online media industry. Skilled in Software and Web Development, UI/Social Media Design, Film Scoring, and Audio Engineering.

# Work Experience

Food Sustainesia Jakarta

Part-time Full-stack Engineer

Feb 2022 - present

- Built, designed, and deployed the company's website, along with their brand website, Eathink.id, using WordPress and Next.is.
- Assisted in designing assets for Eathink's social media content and events organized by Food Sustainesia.

#### Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Tangerang

FTI Laboratory Assistant (Even Semester 2022/2023)

Feb 2023 - Jun 2023

- Taught Algorithms and Data Structures (IF232) and Operating Systems (IF260) courses to secondsemester students.
- Led the creation of the Midterm Exam and Final Exam for both courses, in collaboration with other laboratory assistants.

# Projects

#### PKM UMN: GPdI Hebron Gading Serpong

Link to Website

An ongoing website project by LPPM UMN for our local church in Gading Serpong. In this project, my team and I are working to redesign and rebuild the old website using modern frameworks and tools. My role entails handling all UI/UX related tasks, deploying the website using Vercel, and configuring CI/CD for our workflow

## EDUCATION

## Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Aug 2021 - present

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science (GPA: 3.88/4.0)

SMK Negeri 1 Berau

Aug 2018 - May 2021

Multimedia Department

#### SKILLS

**Programming** Typescript, Javascript, PHP, Java, C/C++, Python

Framework React, Laravel, NextJS, ExpressJS, SvelteKit, TailwindCSS

Creative Tools Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premiere Pro, Ableton Live 11

Last updated: July 6, 2023